얘들아, 밖에 눈이 와
All right! You guys,
it's starting to snow.
못생긴 남자가 막대사탕을
걸고 있어
And look, Ugly Naked Guy
is hanging candy canes.
어디?
Where?
Oh. Well.
성탄절 기분 나네
That's festive.
얘들아,
내 친구 소개해줄게
Guys, there's somebody
I'd like you to meet.
잠깐, 그게 뭐야?
Wait, wait. What is that?
- 마르셀이야, 인사들 해
- 난 싫어
-That's Marcel. Wanna say hi?
-No, I don't.
-He's cute! Where'd you get him?
-My friend Bethel saved him from a lab.
너무 귀엽다!
어디서 났어?
내 친구, 베델이
실험실에서 구해낸 거야
동물 학대하는 친구 이름치고
너무 성스러운 거 아냐?
That is so cruel.
Why would a parent
name their child Bethel?
That monkey's got a Ross on his ass.
원숭이가 로스를
깔고 앉았네
Is he gonna live with you
in your apartment?
오빠, 아파트에서 그 녀석
기를 거야?
응, 캐롤과 헤어진 후
적적했거든
Yeah. It's been kind of quiet
since Carol left.
그냥 사람을 들이지 그래?
Why not get a roommate?
그냥 룸메이트로
정서적으로 안정만 되면...
You reach a certain age, having
a roommate is just kind of pathet
정서적이란 건, 같이 살기
좋다는 뜻이야
That's " pathet. " Sanskrit for
" really cool way to live. "
The One With the Monkey
I' m doing new material tonight.
오늘은 새 노래를 들려줄게
자살한 우리 엄마 주제로 12곡
눈사람 주제로 1곡
I have 1 2 songs about my mother's
suicide and one about a snowman.
눈사람 노래로 시작해
You might wanna open with the snowman.
안녕, 조이
-Hi, Joey.
-Hey, buddy.
- 어이, 친구
- 어서 와
어떻게 됐어?
-So how'd it go?
-I didn't get the job.
일을 안 준대
왜 안 준대?
작년엔 산타클로스 했잖아
How could you not?
You were Santa last year.
Some fat guy's sleeping
with the store manager.
몰라, 어떤 뚱보는
매니저까지 꼬셔봤대
근데 일을 못 땄어
정말 문제야
He's not even jolly.
It's all political.
그럼 어쩔 거야?
-What are you gonna be?
-One of his helpers.
도우미를 하라는데
그건 그만두란 뜻이야
It's just such a slap in the face,
you know?
Do you know what you' re doing
for New Year's?
새해 휴가는 어떻게들
보낼 거니?
- 제발, 관둬라
- 관두자
왜? 뭐 문제 있어?
Hey, what?
What is wrong with New Year's?
너야 문제없겠지
파올로가 있으니까
You have Paolo. You don't have
to face the pressure...
휴가에 끔찍한 부담이
없을 거란 말이야
나는 새해 종이 울리면
뽀뽀할 사람도 없어
...of finding lips to kiss
when the ball drops!
말하고 나니 창피하네
Man, I'm talking loud!
파올로는 새해에 로마에 간대
그러니까 나도 불쌍한 처지야
Paolo's gonna be in Rome
this New Year's.
-I'll be just as pathetic as you.
-Yeah, you wish.
그래, 축하해
좋은 생각이 났어
I've got an idea. Dinner.
- 저녁 식사!
- 좋아!
It's perfect. We'll put it between
lunch and breakfast.
아침과 점심 사이에
저녁을 먹자
사람을 들뜨게 만드는
연휴도 이젠 지겹다
I'm sick of being a victim
of this Dick Clark holiday.
올해는 짝도 없으니까
우리 6명이 저녁이나 하자
I say this year, we make a pact.
Just the six of us. Dinner.
- 좋아, 그러자
- 그러지 뭐
-Sure.
-Fine.
좀더 열광해줄 수 없냐?
I was hoping for more enthusiasm.
- 피비, 준비해
- 알았어
-Phoebe, you' re on.
-Oh, good.
안녕하세요, 신사 숙녀 여러분
피비 부페이 양입니다
Hi. Ladies and gentlemen,
back by popular demand...
... Miss Phoebe Buffay.
감사합니다, 안녕하세요?
Hi. Thanks. Hi.
이맘때면 늘 생각나는 걸
노래로 만들었어요
I wanna start with a song
that means a lot to me.
숯으로 눈을 붙여 눈사람을
만들었는데, 너무 근사했지요
I made a man with eyes of coal
And a smile so bewitching
그때, 우리 엄마가 부엌에서
자살한 건 몰랐답니다
How was I supposed to know
That my mom was dead in the kitchen?
라라라...
엄마 유해는 재가 되고
내 마음도 재가 되어
My mother's ashes
Even her eyelashes
노란 병에 담겨있답니다
Are resting in a little yellow jar
날씨가 추워지면
재채기가 나려고 해요
And sometimes when it's freezing
I feel a little sneezy
And now I Excuse me?
Excuse me? Yeah, noisy boys.
실례, 실례할까요?
거기 수다맨들?
우리 다같이 그 대화에
낄 수 있을까요?
Is it something you'd like
to share with the group?
아뇨, 미안해요
No. No, that's okay.
제 노래도 못 들을 정도로
중요한 얘기라면
If it's important enough
while I'm playing...
여기 모든 이들도
중요하게 생각할 거예요
...it's important enough
for everyone else.
악보를 훔쳐 가면 좋겠다
That guy's going home with a note.
- 저는 제 친구와...
- 좀 크게 말씀해주세요
-I was just saying
-Speak up.
Sorry, l
이 친구에게 당신처럼 아름다운
여자를 본 적 없다고 했어요
I was saying you were the most
beautiful woman I'd ever seen.
그러자 이 친구가...
And he said that Daryl Hannah...
- 다릴 한나 얘기를 했죠
- 다릴 한나요
이 친구는 그 여배우가
제일 예쁘다고 생각해요
...was the most beautiful woman
he'd ever seen.
'스플래쉬'에서는 예뻤지만
'월스트리트'에서는 별로였죠
I said I liked her in Splash,
but not Wall Street.
- 개성이지
- 개성이랄 수 있죠
I thought she had a hard quality.
다릴 한나는
전형적인 미인인 반면에
While Daryl is beautiful
in a conventional way...
당신은 섬세함을 지닌
미인이라는 거죠
...you are luminous
with a kind of delicate grace.
당신이 소리지를 때
알아봤어요
Then that's when you started yelling.
그럼 잠깐 쉬고 하죠
We're gonna take a short break.
악보에, 피비까지 훔쳐가겠다
That guy's going home
with more than a note.
이리와, 마르셀
앉아
Come here, Marcel. Sit here.
아직 키스도 안 했다는 게
믿기질 않아
I can't believe he hasn't
kissed you yet.
파올로는 여섯 번 만나고 나서
내 신체 사이즈를 외웠어
By my sixth date with Paolo,
he'd already named both my breasts.
내가 좀 심한 건가?
Did I just share too much?
아주 조금
Just a smidge.
데이빗은 과학자라
어떤 체계가 있어
David's, like, a scientist guy.
He's very methodical.
- 낭만적인가 봐
- 맞아!
-I think it's romantic.
-Me too!
Did you ever see
An Officer and a Gentleman?
- 너희들 '사관과 신사' 봤니?
- 응
그 영화 주인공과 비슷해
He's kind of like the guy
I went to see that with.
물론, 그이가 더 똑똑하고
더 친절하고 다정하지
Except he's smarter and gentler
and sweeter.
난 그 사람하고
늘 함께 있고 싶어
I just wanna be with him all the time.
낮이나 밤이나
밤이나 낮이나
You know, day and night.
And night and day.
아님 특별한 날에도
And special occasions.
잠깐만! 뭔가 느낌이 온다
신년 파티에 초대할 거지?
I see. You're gonna ask him
to New Year's.
네가 완전히 깨버리는 거야
우린 깨진다!
-She's gonna break the pact.
-No! No, no.
아냐, 아냐, 절대 아냐
No. Yeah, could I just?
그래도 혹시...?
- 부탁해
- 불러, 나도 제니스 불렀어
-Yeah. I already asked Janice.
-What?
네가 제안했다고
네 맘대로야?
This was a pact! This was your pact!
그냥 조바심 나서
덥썩 초대했어
I couldn't handle the pressure.
I snapped!
그래도 제니스는
너무 심한 거 아냐?
But that was the worst breakup
in history!
내가 잘했다는 거 아냐
그냥 급했다니까
I'm not saying it was a good idea.
I snapped!
안녕, 늦어서 미안
Hi, sorry I'm late.
이번엔 진짜 심하다
Too many jokes.
너 조이 맞냐?
Must mock Joey.
신발 죽이지?
Nice shoes, huh?
너 때문에 못 살아
God, you're killing me!
오빠, 집안 살림 좀
만지지 말라고 가르쳐
Ross, he's playing
with my spatulas again!
절대 망가뜨리지 않아
-He's not gonna hurt them, right?
-Do you always have to bring him?
꼭 데리고 다녀야 해?
방에 혼자 두고 싶지 않아
I didn't wanna leave him alone.
We had our first fight this morning.
오늘 아침에 쟤랑
처음 싸움을 했어
내가 늦게까지 일해서 화났대
원치 않아도 해야한다니까
It has to do with my working late.
I said some things that I didn't mean.
똥을 던지더라
He threw some feces.
네가 바쁠 때는 내가 봐줄게
If you're working late,
I can look in on him.
정말 잘됐다!
That would be great!
그런데 쟤한테는 보고싶어서
온 거라고 해줄래?
But make sure it seems
like you're there to see him.
아니면 내가 부탁해서
온 거라고 해
You're not doing it for me.
하지만 녀석이 캐고 들면
난 거짓말 못해
Okay. But if he asks,
I'm not going to lie.
하지만 이 이론은
실험이 불가능해요
But you can't actually
test this theory.
현재 미립자 속도로는
이런 상태 근처도 못 가요
T oday's particle accelerators
aren't powerful enough...
-...to simulate these conditions.
-I have a question then.
- 알았어요, 질문 있어요
- 네
나랑 키스하고 싶을 때 없어요?
-Yeah?
-Do you plan on kissing me ever?
아주 좋은 질문인데요
That's definitely a valid question,
and the answer...
내 답은... '있다'예요
...would be yes. Yes, I was.
네, 하고 싶었죠
하지만 나는 자연 발생적인
순간의 정열적인 키스를 원해요
But I wanted it to be
this phenomenal kiss...
...at a phenomenal moment
because it's you.
- 왜냐면 당신이기 때문에
- 좋아요
Sure.
많이 참다가 하면
더 정열적일 거라 생각했죠
The longer I waited, the more
phenomenal the kiss had to be.
이제 때가 됐으니... 그게...
물건들을 쓸어내고
Now, it's just gotta be
one of those things where l...
당신에게 달려들면서
아주 정열적으로 하죠
...sweep everything off the table.
And I'm not really
a sweeping sort of fella.
David, I think you are
데이빗...
당신은 충분히 할 수 있어요
물리학자라는 껍데기 안에
당신의 정열이 보여요
I mean, you're a sweeper
trapped inside a physicist's body.
그래요?
-Really?
-I'm sure.
네, 확신해요
일단 물건을 쓸고 해봐요
You should just do it. Just throw me.
- 지금... 이요?
- 네, 당장이요
-Now?
-Yeah, right now. Just....
좋아요, 좋아
Okay. Okay. Okay.
이건 좀 비싼 거라서...
You know what?
This is really expensive.
이건 선물이라서
And this was a gift.
- 일일이 다 치우고 하게요?
- 알았어요, 그럼 쓸어버리고
-Now you' re just tidying up.
-Okay.
내가 달려들까요?
아님 당신이 준비할래요?
-You want me to throw you?
-I can hop.
내가 준비하죠
짝없는 동지의 모임이
무슨 뜻인지 모른단 말야?
T ell me something, what does
" no-date pact" mean to you?
정말 미안해
It's just that Chandler
and Phoebe have somebody.
챈들러와 피비가 짝을 초대해서
나도 바비에게 부탁했어
I thought I'd ask Fun Bobby.
- 헤어진 남자친구, 그 바비?
- 응
-Your ex-boyfriend?
-Yeah.
바비가 어디 또 있어?
-You know more than one Fun Bobby?
-I happen to know a Fun Bob.
내 친구 중에도 있거든
자, 커피 나왔어
-Okay. Here we go.
-There's no room for milk.
우유 넣을 자리가 없잖아
됐지? 우유 넣어
There. Now there is.
그럼 우리끼리의 저녁식사에
너희 손님 셋이 온다는 거지?
So on our no-date evening,
three of you now have dates.
- 넷이다
- 넷
-Four.
-Five.
- 다섯
미안해, 파올로가 집에
갔다가 온대
Sorry. Paolo's catching
an earlier flight.
혼자 사는 애 엄마를
만났거든
And I met this really hot
single mom at the store.
나보고 요정 같대
What's an elf to do?
새해 첫 새벽에 나 혼자
우두커니 있는 거야?
So I'll be the only one alone
when the ball drops?
큰 파티에서는 누가
혼자인지 아무도 몰라
We'll have a big party,
and no one will know who's with who.
정말 모든 게 엉망이야
I'll know. This is so not
what I needed right now.
- 무슨 일이야?
- 마르셀 때문에
-What's the matter?
-Oh, it's Marcel.
날 계속 피해 다녀
긴 팔을 질질 끌면서
He's angry with me. I have
no idea why. He keeps shutting me out.
He's walking around all the time,
dragging his hands.
이상하다, 나하고는
어제 밤에 잘 놀았는데
That's weird.
I had a blast with him.
그래?
장난치고 TV보고
던지고 받기도 잘하던데
-Really?
-We played, watched TV.
That juggling thing is amazing.
뭘... 던지고 받아?
What juggling thing?
양말 뭉친 걸로,
네가 가르쳐 준거 아냐?
With the socks?
I figured you taught him that.
아니
No.
그리 어렵지 않아
양말이나 메론만 있으면 돼
It wasn't that big a deal.
Just socks. And a melon.
- 피비! 안녕!
- 안녕, 맥스
-Phoebe!
-Max. Do you know everybody?
- 내 친구들 알죠?
- 아뇨
No. Have you seen David?
데이빗 봤어요?
아뇨, 오늘은 안 왔어요
He hasn't been around.
만나면 빨리 짐 싸서
민스크로 가야한다고 해요
If you see him, tell him to pack.
We are going to Minsk.
민스크?
-Minsk?
-Minsk. It's in Russia.
러시아에 있어요
그건 나도 알아요
I know where Minsk is.
국가 보조금이 나와서
3년간 가 있을 거예요
We got the grant.
Three years, all expenses paid.
민스크에 가는 방법은
그거 하나 뿐이지
And if you're gonna do Minsk,
that's the way to go.
- 언제 떠나는데요?
- 1월 1일에요
-So when do you leave?
-January 1 st.
실례합니다
-Hello?
-What? Hey. Hi.
- 어서 와요
- 안녕!
안녕! 웬일이에요?
-What are you doing here?
-Max told me about Minsk.
민스크 얘기 들었어요
축하해요, 참 좋겠어요
Congratulations! This is so exciting!
네, 친구가 같이 가면
더 좋겠죠
It'd be even more exciting
if we were going.
당신은 안 가요?
왜요?
Oh, you're not going? Oh, why?
어서 말해
T ell her. " I don't wanna go...
"난 민스크에서 립슨과
야마구치랑 일하기 싫어"
...to work with Lipson,
Yamaguchi and Flank.
"아니, 실은, 여기 남아서
여자친구와 잘 해보고 싶어!"
I wanna stay and make out
with my girlfriend! "
그만 해, 고마워
Okay, thank you, Max. Thank you.
정말 안 떠나요?
So you're really not going?
몰라요, 어떻게 해야할 지
당신 곁을 어떻게 떠나야 할 지
I don't know what I'm gonna do.
I just....
How can I leave you?
I just found you.
데이빗...
그치만 어쩔 건데요?
Oh, David. But what are you gonna do?
몰라요, 당신이 결정해봐요
I don't know. You decide.
- 그건 안돼요
- 제발
-Don't do that.
-But l' m asking you.
- 아뇨, 안돼요
- 부탁이에요
- 난 못해요
- 난 결정을 못해요
-I can't make a decision. Just
-Okay. Stay.
좋아요, 가지 마요
- 가지 말라?
- 가지 마요!
-Stay.
이제 아주 잘 하네요
Getting so good at that!
맥스 물건이거든요
It was Max's stuff.
난 이런 파티가 좋아
I love this artichoke thing.
음식 얘긴 하지마
내일부터 다이어트 하거든
Don't tell me what's in it.
The diet starts tomorrow.
제니스 알지?
You remember Janice.
너무 잘 알지
Vividly.
요즘 어때?
-How are you?
-I am fantastic.
너무 좋아
특히, 지금
Now.
놀랄 일이 있어
우리가 다시 만난 지...
It's amazing. We've been back
together for what...
- 10분 됐는데...
- 겨우?
-...Iike 1 0 minutes, and
-ls that all?
그냥 예전과 똑같아
It's like we were never apart.
물론 이별했었지만...
용서하고 잊기로 했지
Of course, we were, but
Forgive and forget.
잊어버려
Well, forget.
- 어서 와요
- 안녕, 샌디에요
-Hi.
-Hi, l' m Sandy.
샌디, 어서 와
Sandy, hi. Come on in.
- 애들을 데려왔소?
- 네, 괜찮죠?
-You brought your kids.
-Yeah. That's okay, right?
파티다!
-Party!
-That thing is not coming in here!
저건 절대 안돼
저거? 파티에 온 손님을
그따위로 대접하니?
This is how you greet guests?
내가 여자친구를 데려왔어도
이런 식으로 할거야?
If I showed up with my new girlfriend,
she wouldn't be welcome?
여자친구라면 탁자에
오줌은 안 싸겠지
Your new girlfriend wouldn't urinate
on my coffee table.
어떻게 면전에서
그런 망신을 주냐?
He was more embarrassed
about that than anyone.
정말 용기를 내서
온 건데 말야
And for him to have the courage
to walk back in here...
아무 일 없던 것처럼
...Iike nothing happened
알았으니까
내 눈에 안 띄게 해
All right. All right.
Just keep him away from me.
고마워
가자, 마르셀
Thank you. Come on, Marcel.
사람들과 어울려 보자구
What do you say you and I mingle?
알았어
All right, I'll catch up
with you later.
나중에 보자구
어머, 레이첼!
Oh, my gosh!
Rachel, honey, are you okay?
괜찮아?
파올로는 어딨어?
-Where's Paolo?
-Rome. Jerk missed his flight.
로마에 있어
비행기를 놓쳤대
그렇게 심하게 화가 났니?
And then your face exploded?
아니
No.
Okay. I was at the airport
getting into a cab...
공항에서 택시를 잡았는데
어떤 여자가 막 소리를 치잖아
...when this woman, this blond
planet with a pocketbook...
...starts yelling. Something
about how it was her cab first.
자기가 먼저 잡았다는 거야
그리고는 내 머리를 잡고
끌어내더라구!
The next thing, she just
starts pulling me out by my hair!
호신용 호루라기를 불었는데
택시만 3대 나타났어
And I was blowing my attack
whistle thingy...
...and three more cabs show up.
So as I'm going to get into a cab,
she tackles me!
그래서 택시를 타려는데
그 여자가 발을 걸어서
머리를 부딪히고
호루라기에 입술이 찧었어
And I hit my head on the curb
and cut my lip on my whistle.
파티는 즐겁니?
Everybody having fun at the party?
먹을 건 남아있어?
-Are people eating my dip?
-Yes.
There.
됐다, 이제 괜찮지?
-That looks okay, right?
-You went a bit wide on the lipstick.
립스틱이 좀 번졌어
- 그래?
- 응
-Oh, I did?
-Yeah.
힘들어죽겠네
눈이 부어서 안 보여
It's hard for me to tell.
My eye's closing up.
내가 고쳐줄게
Let me get it for you.
됐어, 지금 이뻐
-Ow!
-Okay.
You know what? It looks fine.
그럼 나가볼까...
Okay, here we go.
파올로, 코나 깨져라
Screw Paolo,
screw the psycho cab lady.
공항에 그 아줌마도!
송년 파티인데
재밌게 보내야지
It's New Year's Eve.
Let's have a good time.
- 그래
- 자, 나가자
-Okay, here we go.
-Okay.
레이첼, 이쪽이야
All right, there you go. This way.
Here you go.
지난주에 당신을 처음 봤을 때
When I saw you at the store
last week...
요정이 옷을 벗으면
어떨까 상상해봤어요
...it was the first time
I ever mentally undressed an elf.
- 거참... 섹시하겠죠
- 네
-Wow, that's dirty.
-Yeah.
안녕, 얘들아
Hey, kids.
파티 내내 옆에 있기 싫어도
최소한 눈길은 줘야지
He doesn't have to spend
the whole evening with me...
... but at least check in.
여기 있구나!
There you are!
나랑 멀리 있는 거 싫어
You got away from me.
자기가 잘 찾잖아
-But you found me.
-Here, Ross, take our picture.
로스, 사진 찍어 줘
웃어
내 카메라에 찍히는 거야
Smile. You' re on Janice Camera.
죽여라, 아예 죽여
Kill me. Kill me now.
안녕하세요?
레이첼이에요
Hi, l' m Rachel.
누구 친구시죠?
So whose friend are you?
왜 이러지? 다 흘렸네
Look at me, spilling everywhere.
여러분, 바비가 왔어요
Everybody, it's Fun Bobby!
바비! 어서 와
늦어서 미안해
Hey, sorry I'm late.
But my grandfather...
우리 할아버지가
2시간 전에 돌아가셨어
...died about two hours ago.
오늘은 비행기가 없대서
못 가고, 여기 왔어
But I couldn't get a flight
out till tomorrow, so here I am.
어이, 바비!
그간 잘 살았어?
Hey, Fun Bobby! How's it going, man?
Whoa! Who died?
누가 죽기라도 했어?
장례식에 가서 마지막으로
얼굴은 뵈어야지
It's gonna be an open casket,
you know?
So at least I'll get to see him again.
- 바비?
- 왜?
Bobby? Fun Bobby?
바비야!
잠깐 얘기 좀 해
Let me talk to you for just a sec.
최근에 우리 조부모님도
돌아가셔서
I recently lost
a grandparent myself...
충분히 네 심정을 알아
...so I really know exactly
how you feel.
하지만 파티는 망치지마
But you' re really bringing
the party down.
- 미안해, 모니카...
- 괜찮아
-l' m sorry.
-Yeah, yeah, okay.
아주 잘했어, 좋아
There you go. There you go.
사진 나오면, 그 뒤에
'재회 기념'이라고 쓸 거야
I' m gonna blow this one up
and write " Reunited " in glitter.
알았어, 제니스, 그만해!
제니스... 제니스
All right, Janice, that's it!
Janice. Janice.
당신과 다시 잘해보려고
파티에 초대한 건 아냐
Hey, Janice, when I invited you,
I didn't think it meant
아냐, 안돼!
Oh, no!
정말 안돼
오해하게 만들어서 미안해
I' m sorry you misunderstood.
잘 들어, 챈들러!
똑바로 들어!
You listen to me!
계속 이런 식이었지만
이번이 진짜 마지막이야
One of these times, it's just gonna be
your last chance with me!
뭐가 그렇게 신나냐!
Will you give me the thing?
- 안녕, 맥스
- 여우!
-Hi, Max.
-Yoko.
나 혼자 민스크로 갈 거야
I've decided to go to Minsk
without you.
기분은 좀 그렇지만
그래도 민스크잖아
-Wow.
-lt won't be the same...
... but it will still be Minsk.
Happy New Year.
해피 뉴 이어!
괜찮아요?
-Are you all right?
-Yeah, l' m fine. I' m fine.
괜찮아요, 정말
Come on.
민스크로 가요
-You' re going to Minsk.
-No, l' m not going to Minsk.
아뇨, 난 안 가요
꼭 가야 해요
You are so going to Minsk.
온통 민스크 생각만 하면서
나 때문에 있는 건 싫어요
You belong in Minsk.
You can't stay here just for me.
네, 그러면 당신과 이별
해야하는데, 난 그럴 수 없어요
If I go, I have to break up with you.
네, 그럴 수 있어요
-And I can't break up with you.
-Yes, you can.
당신이, "당신을 사랑하지만
내 일은 소명이라 가야하오"
Just say, " Phoebe, I love you,
but my work is my life.
That's what I have to do. "
그럼 나는, "당신 일?
어떻게 그런 말을 하죠?"
And I say, "Your work?
How can you say that? "
당신이, "나도 슬프지만
어쩔 수 없으니, 이해하오"
Then you say, " I have no choice.
Can't you understand that? "
그럼 나는, "아뇨, 싫어요
이해 못해요"
And I say, " No! No!
I can't understand that! "
- 아야
- 미안해요
-Ow.
-Sorry.
그리고 어깨에 손을 얹고...
And then you put
your arms around me.
- 빨리 얹어요
- 미안해요
-Then you put your arms around me.
-Oh, sorry.
사랑한다고,
절대 못 잊는다고 해요
And then you tell me you love me
and you'll never forget me.
절대 못 잊어요
I'll never forget you.
자정이 다 됐으니 가세요
새해 추억을 갖고 싶지 않아요
Then you say that you have to go...
... because you don't wanna start the
year with me if you can't finish it.
당신이 보고 싶을 거예요
과학자 아저씨
I' m gonna miss you,
you scientist guy.
안녕하세요, 타임스 광장의
딕 클락입니다
Hi, Dick Clark in Times Square.
이곳에 꽃 색종이가
뿌려지고 있는데요
We're in a virtual snowstorm
of confetti here in Times Square.
매년 더 많아지는군요
It gets better every....
잘 자네
Here you go, kids.
그리고 새한테 물렸어요
And then the peacock bit me.
자정 되면 키스할래요?
Please kiss me at midnight!
샌디 봤어?
말해도 될지 모르겠지만
-You seen Sandy?
-I don't know how to tell you this...
샌디는 괴짜 과학자 맥스랑
침실에 있어
... but she's in the bedroom
getting it on with Max.
이렇게 말을 잘하다니!
Oh, I did know how to tell you.
얘들아, 때가 됐다
-Hey, everybody, the ball is dropping.
-What?
뭐?
때가 됐다구!
The ball is dropping!
20초 후면 자정이 됩니다
In 20 seconds, it'll be midnight.
기쁨의 시간이 왔도다
And the moment of joy is upon us.
왜 우린 뭘 해도
짝이 없는 거지?
Looks like that no-date pact
worked out.
다들 행복해 보여서
심술이 나
Everybody looks so happy.
I hate that!
전부 다는 아냐,
바비?
Not everybody is happy. Hey, Bobby!
3... 2... 1!
새해 축하해!
four, three, two...
...one! Happy New Year!
내가 머리를 써봤어
그리 똑똑한 머린 아니지만
I thought I'd throw this out.
I' m no math whiz...
여자 셋, 남자 셋
짝이 맞잖아
... but I do believe there are
three girls and three guys right here.
키스할 기분이 안 나
I don't feel like kissing
anyone tonight.
난 하고 싶어도 못해
-I can't kiss anyone.
-So, I'm kissing everyone?
그럼 내가 다 해줘?
아니, 로스랑은 안돼
오빠잖아
No, you can't kiss Ross.
That's your brother.
맞아
아주 기분 죽인다
나만 왕따구나
So now everybody's
getting kissed but me.
누가 키스 좀 해줘
나한테 뽀뽀 좀 해!
Somebody kiss me.
새해 첫 새벽이야!
뽀뽀하자, 자정이야!
Somebody kiss me! It's midnight!
Somebody kiss me!
알았어, 됐지?
All right! All right!
There!
정말 잘해주고 싶었어
아직도 사랑한다구
I wanted this to work so much.
I'm still in there.
기저귀 갈아주고
이도 잡아주지
Changing his diapers.
Picking his fleas.
그래도 모른척이야
But he's just phoning it in.
아무 것도 모르는 누군가를
짝사랑하는 거, 힘든 거 알지?
It's hard that something you love
so much doesn't love you back.
그 여자가 내 이빨까지 깼나봐
I think that bitch cracked my tooth.